Just
Just as that servant likes it
The Prophet said
Let it be clear,
that is nothing except his
tidraj
Is a gradual approach to get
him
caught up
In the punishment of Allah
He is gradually being wrapped
up
The punishment will soon wrap
him up
For he is made to forget
He is given the chance to
forget
that he will be caught up one
day
So that explains that verse
we read
When Allah said
When they forget what they
have been
reminded of
We will open for them the
gates
of everything
So that when they rejoice in
what
they have been given
They will take what they have
been
given
So that they will be blessed
We beg Allah to protect us
all
Brothers
When you get everything you
want on
sinfulness
You are up on a river
You are up on yahu
You make ritual killings to
gain wealth
You steal the money belonging
to government
You are a court judge